- Dude, crazy
story this morning.
- Gotta hear it.
- All right.
- Heist in the news.
-This one comes in from Dino.
Shout out to Dino.
- Dino's my man.
- Headline reads-
"armored truck kills money
on Texas freeway, sparking
cash grab frenzy."
- Feels awesome.
- Here we go.
"An armored truck dropped loads
of cash onto the Dallas
Thornton Freeway,
causing a major traffic jam .
Motorists hopped out of their
autos, scooping up the bills.
Authorities say drivers
need to return the money
or face possible
criminal charges."
- I saw this on Tic-Tac.
People running around
the freeway yanking cash.
- Awesome, I
mean, I know I'd do it.
- And filming themselves.
- Smart.
- According to
the National Weather Service...
- ... of revised
river forecast
for lower Tallapoosa
and Alabama Rivers.
- Hey there, I'm
meteorologist Dick Duchie
here with a look at your
First Alert Forecast.
Get ready for a-
- I feel like I failed my wife.
I feel like I failed my kids.
I kept telling myself that
I didn't have a problem,
but when I woke up
in my daughter's room
with holes punched in her walls,
that's when I finally
realized how deep I was.
It didn't matter though.
My wife already packed the car
two hours before I woke up.
I don't even know where
they are anymore.
- Thanks for sharing.
I mean, that's what the
bottle does to us, right?
It makes you a liar.
You become your worst self and
worst version of ourselves.
That's the hardest
part, I think,
admitting what you've become.
I know it took me a long,
long time to admit that.
I know that if it wasn't for
this group and, and my, my son,
I'd be at the bottom
of a glass somewhere.
That's, that's without
question, so...
- Hey, um...
Sorry for losing it back there.
Not a good first impression.
- Please.
My first meeting I was rocking
in a fetal position for hours.
It gets better.
That's me.
Keep coming back.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Settle down.
Just making sure you heard me.
You know how old
people's hearing is, huh?
- Well I'll tell you what,
maybe if you keep smarting off,
the horn won't be the
only thing screaming.
- Okay, settle down or you're
not getting your lunch.
- Go, go, go.
Let's go.
So, uh, what's on
Sarah's menu today?
- Peanut butter and pickles.
- Ooh.
How much longer you gonna
be able to stay on this diet?
- Honestly, it's not
as bad as you think.
- Yeah, it is.
- Look, you can judge
me all you want,
but all the books say that
the more we do together,
the more it's like
we're both pregnant.
- Ha!
- Which, it's
it's a good thing, I think.
Speaking of which, actually,
Sarah said she didn't get
your RSVP for the baby shower.
Sent them out a week ago.
I, I told her they
probably got lost in the mail.
So, did it get lost in the mail?
- I don't know.
- Dad, is everything okay?
- Yeah.
- No, I, I know, I know.
I was thinking about
her last night too.
- Sarah would go over baby names
and this one's gonna be a boy,
but she really wants the
next one to be a girl.
So you throw out
the name Trisha,
that's a possibility
down the line.
And I dunno, I wasn't
sure how you'd take that.
- Good name.
- Yeah.
Well, hey, six years
sober today, big guy. Huh?
Come on.
She'd be proud of you, Dad.
- 59326.
- Yep.
- 57291.
- You do know how long
your route is today, right?
You guys are doing the dead 10
and you're already
late. As always.
Tell me, you really need to
review all this stuff again?
- It's protocol, Frank.
- Protocol is to get
this shit back in the truck
so I can get back to
my clients, James.
- In a better mood than usual.
- 20248.
49826.
- Got it.
- Pull that.
- Yeah.
- Fucking hot box in here.
Shit.
It's not even noon
and it's this hot.
This thing work?
Oh my god.
The hell's that guy hauling?
- It's not our business.
- All right.
I got it, I got it.
You okay?
- Oh fuck.
- You all right?
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
I dropped a fucking pen.
Fuck.
- What do you mean a pen?
- A pen light.
Sarah gave me this light with
my name on it specifically
'cause I'm always losing
shit in this fucking truck.
- Let's go.
Come on.
- Fuck it.
Fuck it, let's go.
Okay, it's fine.
- Look, I don't know
what's in there,
but if we break it, we buy it.
- I got it.
- You understand that?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Look, can you just don't
tell Sarah about this, okay
'cause then she's gonna
start worrying about
me losing my gun next
and it's gonna turn
into a whole thing.
- What, what is the
real issue here?
- There's no issue, I just
don't want her to stress
until the baby comes.
- About a pen?
- Yeah, it's gonna
stress her out.
- Little words of wisdom.
Your stress starts when
that baby pops its head out.
You got that?
- Dad, please.
- Fine.
I will not tell Sarah
that you lost a pen light
with your little initials on it.
Yeah.
Nothing more stress free
than driving a cash truck
10 miles to
bumfuck nowhere.
Beautiful, beautiful
- Dad? You all right?
- Yeah.
- Fucking truck's falling apart.
- It's got a little
bit of character to it.
- Hey.
Am I gonna have
to twist your arm
or are you gonna finally
come over for dinner tonight?
- I, uh, I have to host a
meeting tonight, I'm sorry.
- You know you have an actual
family outside that circle?
- Yeah, but not one
that's gonna drive a truck
through the living room.
- Not yet anyways.
All right, look, the
offer still stands. Okay?
Just come over whenever.
Just thought it'd be
a good idea for you to
get away from your
vices for a bit.
- Case.
You want me to bring a pie or...
- Careful with the C4?
- Man, I, I know
it's unstable as fuck, man.
- Well, everything's unstable.
- Speak for yourself.
- Yeah, you're late.
No, we're ready. Are
you fucking ready?
Right.
Let's do it.
- Hey, except that it's the
truth.
- No, it's not. No it's not.
- Uh, it's the truth.
First day, little
Case on the job,
a little baby in
his Kevlar vest.
Got his baby, new little id,
it's right off the
press still hot,
carrying his first bag of money.
Big bag of money.
He's so nervous, he's, I
would say raining sweat.
- He's exaggerating.
- You left a trail
on the sidewalk, there's
no question about this.
Anyway, back to the truth.
All jittery, like, somebody
comes up beside him
and taps him on the shoulder
just to ask the time.
He whips around like Dirty
Harry right in the face
of 147-year-old woman.
- Okay, calm down.
She was probably in her fifties.
- Maybe 128.
- And I'm regretting inviting
you to this dinner already.
- Oh, ah. I'm glad you did.
I needed a homecooked meal.
- Yep, and I needed
a good laugh.
Well, cheers to 30 days
on the job as a team.
- Cheers.
- So how was the route today?
Any old lady try and
knock over the truck?
- Okay, very funny,
baby. Thank you.
No, no old ladies. No nothing.
Just, just nice and quiet.
- That's how me and
the little guy like it.
- I, I don't know.
I, I'd kill for some
action, honestly.
I mean, just one
tweaker with a gun
so I have an excuse to
pull my taser at least.
- You are gonna find that
the best action is no action.
Trust me on that.
- Jeremy really let out the
waterworks this time, huh?
- First week's the
hardest, you know that.
- Yeah, you know
more than anyone.
Hey, you hang in there, brother.
Another year clear is
another year to stumble.
- Right.
Thanks, Pete.
- Hey, looks like you're
moving slow today.
Frank's gonna be pissed.
- Always is.
So what's on the menu today?
- Turkey and fluff.
- You're late again.
I needed these things
outta here 10 minutes ago.
- There was traffic, Frank.
- I'll bet.
Come on, Brody, I don't
have time for these excuses.
I have a bank full of
people waiting for me.
- Why are there four cases?
Only says three here.
- What?
Why do you care?
Just haul the stuff.
- There are rules
and protocols, Frank,
and this clipboard doesn't
say anything about this case.
- The clipboard, yeah?
What does it say about
me calling your boss
and telling him you're
coming late to work
because you're going
to AA meetings?
Maybe he doesn't know
that you were kicked off
the force for being a drunk.
Listen, Brody, I hate
to break it to you,
but you're not a cop anymore.
You're a mailman with a gun.
Just deliver the mail.
- Dad?
You're squeezing the wheel.
- It's gonna be okay, we got
plenty of room back there.
- Except people get arrested.
We don't know what's
in those cases.
It could be anything.
Could be laundered money,
it could be unmarked bills,
we could be fencing something.
If it's not on the
ledger, we don't take it.
It's my fault.
It's my responsibility.
Shoulda said no to that prick.
- So, what you're saying is
this might not be
a nice quiet ride.
- Let's try to make it one.
- Dad?
Dad? Hey.
Dad, what's going on?
- Hold on.
Shit!
What is going on?
Fuck!
Man, where the hell
did they come from?
- Case, call it in.
Call it in.
- Dispatch, this is
Casey to dispatch.
We are getting robbed
on Lincoln Road
and we need backup,
do you hear me?
Do you copy?
They're not fucking answering.
- Try another channel.
Shit!
Fuck!
- Hold on.
- Fuck.
They're not fucking answering!
- Hello.
This is 432, this is
Brody, 247, we have...
Hello?
- What happened?
- We're being jammed,
we're being jammed.
- He's on the right!
- It's closed!
- What the
hell is this guy doing?
- Dad?
- Let's go!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Come on, come on.
- Left door opening.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- On top, on
top, they're armed!
- Listen to me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Breathe, you can do this.
Both do three shots,
tight grouping.
You go low, I go high.
Wait for the reload.
Now!
- I think I got him.
- Guys, Viper!
Viper!
Motherfucker!
- Motherfucker!
- Go!
- I feel like there's like
this fucking pulse in my leg.
- Jesus, armor
piercing bullets
Hey, it went clean through,
it went clean through.
Okay.
- Does that mean
I'm gonna die?
- Not if you calm down,
you're gonna slow your heart,
you're gonna slow your heart.
Nice, deep breaths, ready?
- Yeah.
- Deep, even.
- Motherfucker!
You sold me on an easy pick.
- It was supposed
to be an easy pick.
- Yeah, well, your easy
pick just fucking shot me.
- You'll live.
- Okay.
- That fucking stings.
- Calm down.
Pressure.
Pressure, okay?
Hold this.
- Hawk!
Viper and Hawk are down, man.
- Shit.
- They're gone.
These assholes locked
themselves in the truck.
- Fuck!
Breathe.
- Fuck, fuck.
What's that one for?
- Breathe.
That's it.
Calm down, calm down.
Calm down.
- Blow the
fucking doors off.
- That won't happen.
- Why not?
Where's Match?
- All over the bridge.
- Okay, okay, calm.
Okay.
Just gotta hold till
they, till they come.
Till they send backup.
- How? We don't have
a radio or a phone.
- We got no service.
- How? We're not
even that remote.
- They're using jammers.
Push down, push down.
Okay.
These guys are pros.
- Dad.
What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
- Anybody home?
What we have here is a
Murphy's Law situation.
You know what that is?
You're old enough to know what
Murphy's law is right, James?
- You know my name.
- Research.
Hey, Casey, sorry you
got pulled into this.
So, Murphy's Law is this:
if something can go
wrong, it will go wrong.
At the worst possible time.
Like this fucking moment.
- So I guess you didn't
plan on me sending
two of your boys
up in smoke, huh?
- Correct.
- Hey, you know my name. What
am I supposed to call you?
- So, now it's a chess match?
- Looks like that.
- You can call me Rook.
- More like Pawn.
- Listen, don't waste time.
Come out now.
It's not your money, okay?
Your kid is shot, he's got what?
What do you got, Casey?
Maybe four hours?
Be smart.
You come out now and we'll
get you to a hospital,
you got my word.
Come on, be smart.
- Look, don't bullshit
me, we both know
you didn't do this plan to
keep two witnesses alive.
And if you could blow
these doors open,
you wouldn't be here
negotiating with me.
My guess is Plan A
went up with your boys.
- Bad choice.
Let's go.
- Was that guy right?
- If we open the
doors, we're dead.
- Okay.
Yeah, you're right.
I'll take the chance.
He said he's been
following us, right?
He's seen our ledger.
We don't carry that
much this early.
- This doesn't make sense.
The armor piercing
rounds, cell jammers.
Seven paramilitary
units fighting over
a hundred grand is...
a 14 grand split.
Shit.
- What the fuck?
- It's millions.
That's a whole lot of gold.
- Who does it belong to?
- It's millions.
That signia?
It's cartel.
I saw that on the force.
Okay, now we know.
- What is that?
- Tear gas?
- Close your eyes.
- The case, Dad.
Use the cases, us
the foam in the case.
Hook it up.
Plug up all the vents.
- It's still coming in.
- That rent-a-cop's some
tough son of a bitch
to take that much gas.
- We're outta foam, Dad.
- Think there's a chance
that they just scorched
their lungs and passed out.
- Hey, Rook. That all you got?
Stay calm. A little gas?
- These fuckers must have
plugged up the holes.
God...
This is a fucking shitshow.
Hey!
James, you wanna
know what a steel can
plus a bayou heat equals?
Two wannabe cops
roasted by sundown!
- Oh, by the
way, I found the gold.
- Son of a bitch.
- Just wondering when
you try to fence that
to some gang in Mexico,
what's gonna happen
when they find out
that it's cartel?
Think about that?
- James, James, listen!
You touch a coin in
that fucking case,
and I promise you and your kid
are gonna go down real hard.
- Then I guess
you better move fast.
- Get the drill.
Get the drill!
- Cut that shit out!
- What is your problem, man?
- Your voice, Tex.
Keep it in your mouth.
This goddamn world's
ugly enough as it is.
- You could've made
me slip a wing nut,
and then where'd we be?
- How much longer?
- Well, Mama always said
you can get it done faster
or you can get it done right.
- Yeah?
Well, if you don't crack
that truck open soon
I'm gonna crack you open.
Fucking shitshow.
- Asshole.
Just saying, I managed
to sing at the 44 Club.
What do you listen to, Warrant?
Fucking Marilyn Manson?
Shit.
- Yeah, the heat's
getting to him.
Couple more hours out here
and he's gonna turn on us.
- No, he'll be all right.
- Bullshit, Rook.
- He'll be all right, relax.
- That's bullshit.
He is this close to going postal
because the last score
didn't go like this.
You sold us on a
snatch and grab.
Throw some fireworks at
the door, tase the drivers
and then book it to Mexico.
- You don't have the
stomach for this,
then leave while you can.
Let's go!
- Sarah would be pissed
if she saw this scar.
I mean, they say
chicks dig scars,
but this is fucking crazy.
- Let's just get you
back to Sarah now, okay?
We gotta clean that
out, it's festering.
- Here.
- No, it's an infection,
we have to take care
of that infection.
We're gonna need some alcohol.
- I don't mean to
tempt you, Dad,
but I would kill for
some moonshine right now.
- What about vodka?
- That would work too,
but I don't think there's
gonna be any vodka in here.
- I got a thermos
full of vodka.
- It's gonna be all right.
Calm down, all right?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Sure .
- Fucking lunatic.
- Dad, you've been
drinking again.
- I never, I never
really stopped.
I...
I tried, I, I did, I just...
You know, I filled
that thermos every day,
and I'd go tell addicts
to keep clean and I was...
- All this time you've
just been lying to me?
- I tried.
Your mother and I just, you,
you wouldn't understand.
- Don't say that, don't say...
I remember more than you know.
- This is so humiliating.
- What?
Kidding me?
These people, they'd give
the right arm to be able
to camp next to a gator's nest.
Your left ankle.
- Oh.
- Your elbow.
- Elbow.
- Your wife.
- Hey!
Well, most people aren't
stuffed in a cop car.
We look like criminals.
- I think this is sweet.
I think I'm riding
shotgun into a raid.
- My man Case.
See? Respects the old man's job.
Somebody does in this car.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Mother has a total
disrespect for the law.
- Oh, it's
dark as pitch out there.
- It is, there's no lights.
That maniac.
- You're off duty.
- They can kill somebody.
- Dad, come on.
- Look at him.
- Okay, you are off duty.
- I gotta talk to him,
he's gotta slow down.
It's okay.
- Babe.
- Two minutes, come on now.
Hand me my gun?
Please.
- No.
Seriously?
- He can hurt somebody.
All right, stay in the car.
License and registration.
- You don't look like a cop.
- License and registration, kid.
You're going 100 in a
50, you aware of that?
- Yes sir. It
won't happen again.
- Yeah?
See, I was in a good
mood because I'm taking
my family camping and
then I got in a bad mood
when you rocketed past us.
I wanna get in a
good mood again.
So, Mr. Corey
Marshon, if I find out
that you're going two miles
over the speed limit anywhere
in this county, I'm
taking you to jail.
Do you understand that?
- Yes, sir.
- Slow down.
We're on the move.
What?
- You said you wouldn't do this.
- It was a little
stop, it's over.
He was driving a hundred miles
an hour, he'd kill somebody.
- Dad, really?
- All right.
No more cop, I promise.
Sorry.
- Yes,
engine five is arriving.
Dispatch requesting
medvac at scene.
- Sir, are you okay?
Sir?
Guys, I need you
to come down here.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
- You go on the
other side.
- Ma'am, are you
all right ?
- I hated you.
I wished it was you.
I wished it was
you instead of her.
I was so angry.
I must've went through 15
pillows I punched 'em so hard.
And we told you, Dad.
We told you not to
stop, just keep driving,
but you just had to
turn on those lights.
Just had to turn
on those lights.
But you didn't drive
that truck into Mom.
And you need to stop
punishing yourself
for something that you
had no control over.
She wouldn't want that.
I think it's just, it hurts,
it hurts to admit she's gone
because of a stupid accident.
- We gotta move and
we gotta this thermos.
Just gotta find something we
can get through that latch.
Over there.
No, turn your head.
There's still gas
in that, get back.
- Okay.
Keep it going.
- More. More.
- Okay, all right.
- That does not look good.
- This is taking
forever.
- I don't think he's bluffing.
Those doors look like
they're about to pop already.
- How many bullets you got?
- Dropped my gun on the bridge,
all I got left is a bug zapper.
Here.
- We can make these
tasers work I think,
then we cut it to two.
- Yeah, yeah, just
two heavily armed pros
with armor-piercing bullets.
I'm sure our bare hands are
more than enough against that.
What are you doing?
- Unless...
We got a lighter and
some high-proof alcohol.
Let's even the odds.
- Dad, a Molotov in this tight
space, I mean, it's suicide.
My leg's covered in that stuff.
One little mistake
and we'll all go up.
- Now let's get some air.
Can you make it?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Come on.
- She's gonna crack any second!
It's gonna crack any
second!
- Stop! Stop!
Please!
Please stop, I can't
take this anymore!
- Cut it.
What'd you say?
- I can't take it
anymore.
I'll come out, okay?
I'll come out.
I need to get to a hospital.
Just take me to a
hospital, please.
- The
kid's doing an act.
- Please, stop.
Take me to a hospital, please.
- All right.
- What do we do?
- The kid's doing an act.
Don't you go soft
belly on me now.
- This is not your
show, you get it?
Are we clear on that?
- You're gonna let
these two fuckers out?
Keep that shit going!
Now!
- Our time doubles
with a homicide,
so we're gonna try
every chance we can.
Work with me, man.
Checkmate, James.
There's only one
way outta this thing
where you're still breathing.
Hey Casey, three seconds
to open up the door.
One.
Two.
Three!
Go get the C4 in the van, go on.
- Holy fuck.
- Come on!
- Don't miss your chance,
'cause it's closing.
Closing fast.
Come on, kid, don't be stupid.
You can still walk
away with your life,
you just gotta open up.
- What about my dad?
- He's already marked his grave,
don't bring yourself
down with him.
- You know, I'd
like to trust you,
but let's face it,
besides everything else,
you're all really
bad fucking liars.
- Open the fucking hatch!
We're gonna get in there
one way or the other,
that I can promise you.
- Motherfuckers, you
fucking amateurs!
- Have you lost
your fucking mind!
- These two are dead!
- If you keep firing
with that impact blast,
you're gonna tear
through us first!
- Yeah, you know, you
really are the motherfucker
of all jinxes, do you know that?
Who did the scouting?
- I did,
you psychotic asshole.
I'm the only reason you
know about this score!
- Oh, yeah, and this job
has been a fucking disaster!
- Ask yourself
what you want more,
the money or a
bullet in your head.
- Our demo guy's
all over the bridge,
our driller's toast
and this little bitch
won't even let me smoke
these two rent-a-cops.
You better come
up with something,
you cocksucking bastard.
- Is that a threat?
- How long have we
known each other, huh?
A dozen years?
That's not a threat, my friend.
Call it a forewarning.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Let's get this
thing over with.
- This fucking guy.
- Are you hit?
- I don't think so.
- Thank god that guy
can't shoot for shit.
- All good in there?
Tensions are running high.
You might say we're
at a stalemate.
Agreed?
- What do you want?
- What do I want?
If I had guys like
you on my side,
this job would've
been over hours ago.
There's only one way out, Casey.
Don't take too long.
- It's getting hotter in here.
We're gonna be cooking
in another hour.
Drink it.
- I'm fine.
- I'm not asking.
Come on.
Do you believe in miracles?
- No.
There's good luck and
there's bad luck, that's it.
- Finish it then.
- Case.
Thank you.
- Yeah, it'll cool off.
- Radio's still silent.
- How long do you think
it'll stay that way?
- Well it's a
hail-fucking-Mary miracle
we haven't been picked up yet.
I say we move.
- And do what?
- Ram that truck off the bridge.
- Yeah.
- Those doors will
bust open easy.
- Just lose the gold
in the river, yeah.
- Depending on the depth, yeah.
I mean, I can swim.
Can you, Jinx?
- Hey, they're gonna run out
of air soon enough, okay?
- That old man would be dead
if you didn't pull your shot.
Part of me thinks
you want him to live.
- It's the last fucking
time with this guy.
It's the last time.
- We never had problems like
this when it was just us.
- We never went after
this much fucking money.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- We never lost
anyone before either.
I say we drop the whole lot,
take the gold for ourselves.
- Can you move your toes?
- Yeah, yeah.
- That's good.
Case...
I'm sorry.
You were right.
I haven't been
there for you and,
I mean, I should have been.
You were for me, and
you coulda cut out
at any time, you didn't.
- What kind of dad would
I be if I did that?
Hey.
If we do get outta here,
you gotta stick around,
be a grandpa for a little bit.
I know these last six
years were a lie, but
I need these next six
months to be straight.
Can you do that?
- Yeah.
I promise you.
- What the fuck is it gonna
take to break these two?
- They will soon.
- When?
When the APB's out on us?
Come on, let's waste
these assholes now.
- Soon.
- You really want
sirens on our ass
to the border, don't you?
- You know, we could
find a different score
that doesn't involve murder.
- You are a fucking piece
of work, you know that?
You're gonna back out now, hmm?
And you.
You, my friend, have lost it.
- The plan was, and
is, they don't die.
- After everything
that's happened.
- I'm not bringing any
more fucking heat,
what's with you?
You going crazy?
- I'm gonna get that
gold no matter what.
- Now what?
- This is my show now.
My way now.
- These guys
are fucking crazy.
- They're gonna push
us off the bridge.
Don't move.
- Hold on!
Stop, stop, stop!
Listen to me, listen to me.
You did everything
you could, okay?
We're both gonna die
if you stay here.
Just go.
We're both gonna die, just go.
Dad, I can't.
I can't, just go, just go.
Dad.
- Come on.
Let me catch my breath,
and then I'll get you home.
I'll get you home.
Come on.
Lean on it for a sec.
Sit down.
- You're survivors.
- What are you
gonna do now, huh?
What are you gonna do?
- I'm not a killer.
Not in my nature.
I'm done.
- What does that mean?
- It means what it means, James.
- What are you asking?
- When those cops show up in
a minute, I was never here.
- You're aware I
was a cop, right?
- Ain't nobody's perfect.
- You all right with that, Case?
- Thanks.
- Drive.
- Come on.